Contact

Springfield, OH 937-284-1277 (Mobile) marmstrongmsn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/melissaarmstrong-msn-rn-84a28762 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Oncology
Palliative Care

Melissa Armstrong MSN, RN

Nurse Manager at Ohio Valley Surgical Hospital Springfield, Ohio

Summary

Experienced Clinical Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Leadership, EPIC, Clinical Research, Nursing Education, Palliative Care, Oncology, and Emergency Room Nursing. Strong professional leader with a Master's degree focused in Nursing with an Emphasis in Leadership from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

Ohio Valley Surgical Hospital Nurse Manager June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Springfield, Ohio

Kettering Health Network Clinical Nurse Manager September 2015 - February 2018 (2 years 6 months) SOIN Beavercreek, OH

The Ohio State University
Administrative Nursing Supervisor
December 2012 - September 2015 (2 years 10 months)
The James Cancer Hospital

Springfield Regional Medical Center Patient Advocate Manager April 2010 - April 2012 (2 years 1 month)

Good Samaritan Hospital Oncology and Palliative Care Nurse Manager July 1992 - May 2010 (17 years 11 months)

Education

Grand Canyon University

Master's degree, Nursing with an Emphasis in Leadership · (2012)

Capital University

Bachelor's degree, Nursing · (2005 - 2006)

Kettering College of Medical Arts

Associate's degree, Nursing · (1989 - 1992)